Nupur Morning, tell me
which are the important triggers and
where will the action be seen on the basis of the news. Absolutely, good morning.
First of all, as we were discussing, the
RBI policy is about to come, on which the
entire market will be focused. Also, the
meeting of the NDA parliamentary party is going to take place
today at 2:00 PM, so this is
also a politically important event, where we have to keep an
eye. Cash results of PTC India are
coming today, so we have to keep the focus here. Earlier, the
company had postponed its results,
today finally its results will be seen coming.
In the HDFC AMC BoT meeting, the
company will be seen considering the dividend. The
process of buy back of Anand ATI will start from today,
it will continue till June 13. See the price, it is
around ₹ 450 and it will be done through a tender offer.
Its size is ₹ 165 crore. It is
a state. You will see the dividend adjustment of ICSA Loba General Insurance
Company 6 here. The
final
dividend adjustment of ₹ 10 in India Mat Inter will also be
visible here. Indian Hotels 1.75
You will see the adjustment today in the
form of dividend and Indian Bank will
focus here and an adjustment of ₹1 will be seen here as well. In
terms of news,
see positive news coming for Vipra where the
company was seen getting an order of ₹4175 crore from a US-based sub-
service provider company. The
managed service company will
provide some products. This order has been given for a period of 5 years.
RVNL where the
company has
received a big order of around ₹500 crore for civil work from NTPC. You will see the
company completing it in 66 months.
Bajaj Finance will be monitored
because the IPO of the company's subsidiary Bajaj Housing
Finance has been approved by the board.
In the IPO, you will see about
000 crore being raised through preferential issue and OFS.
You will see Ro Moto Corp where the
company has bought an additional 2.2% stake in associate company Ather Energy.
This is worth ₹124 crore.  The transaction is between
AAA Bank and AAA Securities, where
SEBI has issued an administrative warning
letter regarding the delisting of ICICI Securities, where
this letter has been issued on the appeal to vote in favor of delisting of ICICI. The appeal made by ICICI Bank to the
shareholders to vote in favor of de-merger has been
accused here, so
both these stocks will be in focus today. Union
Bank of India, where the board
meeting is going to be held on June 11, will be seen raising funds through rights issue and IB
preferential allotment. The
focus is on Canvin Homes, where the
board is seen approving raising
1000 crores through IB preferential allotment rights issue. The
record date for dividend has also been fixed as July 18, 2024.
PB Fitech is sentimental negative
news for the company, where the
chairperson and CEO of the company are
shown receiving show cause notice from the CB, the
company has given Y.
17 crores was invested in NP Marketing Management due to which
these notices are now being seen coming.
United Burries has positive news from the
company where it has
now launched a new brand Queen Fisher Premier Larger Beer in the Maharashtra market, so the
focus will be on this and lastly
IRB Infra where if we
look at the total toll data in the month of May, it is
shown to be increasing by 30% on YOY basis. So these are some important news
on which you have to keep an eye. Thank you,
come for details.